<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Jupitara Ray</title><link>https://jupitararay.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Jupitara Ray</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://jupitararay.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Typography Styles &amp; Element Examples</title><link>https://jupitararay.github.io/elements/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 12:27:33 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://jupitararay.github.io/elements/</guid><description>Font Sizes A A A A A A A A 6rem
(96px) 5rem
(80px) 3rem
(48px) 2.25rem
(36px) 1.5rem
(24px) 1.25rem
(20px) 1rem
(16px) .875rem
(14px) Type Samples Head&amp;shy;line Sub&amp;shy;head&amp;shy;line Level 1 Heading One page to rule them all...well, not really. This page displays sample typography and page elements to illustrate their style. Things like headings and paragraphs showing the beautiful type scale, form elements, tabular data, and image layouts just to name a few.</description></item><item><title>Contributors</title><link>https://jupitararay.github.io/contributors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jupitararay.github.io/contributors/</guid><description>Thank you to all the folks who have contributed both technical and creative skills to this project:
Desirée De Leon 🦒 (designed 5 of the custom color themes, made illustrations for the workshop, and provided general aesthetic feedback along the way)
Garrick Aden-Buie 🧙‍♀️ (debugged headroom.js and lent his panelset.js code to the theme)
Allison Horst 🐕 (awesome illustrations of campfires, seedlings, and evergreens, as well as my R Markdown hedgehog mascot 🦔)</description></item><item><title>License</title><link>https://jupitararay.github.io/license/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jupitararay.github.io/license/</guid><description>My blog posts are released under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://jupitararay.github.io/myprojects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jupitararay.github.io/myprojects/</guid><description>Vowel Space Area Variation in Assamese Dialects In this study, I explore the sociophonetic variation in the vowel space of Assamese, in order to provide an empirical account of language variation and change in a socioeconomic context.
A Phonological Description of Koch Rajbongshi I am currently working on developing a phonological description of Koch Rajbongshi, an Indo-Aryan language spoken in parts of northeast India and Bangladesh.
Infant Speech Babbling Patterns in Kabyle-Berber I collaborated with my colleagues Dalila Gauoa and Jackson Kellog on a project where we studied the speech patterns of a Kabyle-Berber speaking infant, to understand if babbling patterns exhibited in children are truly universal.</description></item></channel></rss>