<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Jupitara Ray</title><link>https://jupitararay.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Jupitara Ray</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://jupitararay.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Typography Styles &amp; Element Examples</title><link>https://jupitararay.github.io/elements/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 12:27:33 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://jupitararay.github.io/elements/</guid><description>Font Sizes A A A A A A A A 6rem
(96px) 5rem
(80px) 3rem
(48px) 2.25rem
(36px) 1.5rem
(24px) 1.25rem
(20px) 1rem
(16px) .875rem
(14px) Type Samples Head&amp;shy;line Sub&amp;shy;head&amp;shy;line Level 1 Heading One page to rule them all...well, not really. This page displays sample typography and page elements to illustrate their style. Things like headings and paragraphs showing the beautiful type scale, form elements, tabular data, and image layouts just to name a few.</description></item><item><title>Contributors</title><link>https://jupitararay.github.io/contributors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jupitararay.github.io/contributors/</guid><description>Thank you to all the folks who have contributed both technical and creative skills to this project:
Desirée De Leon 🦒 (designed 5 of the custom color themes, made illustrations for the workshop, and provided general aesthetic feedback along the way)
Garrick Aden-Buie 🧙‍♀️ (debugged headroom.js and lent his panelset.js code to the theme)
Allison Horst 🐕 (awesome illustrations of campfires, seedlings, and evergreens, as well as my R Markdown hedgehog mascot 🦔)</description></item><item><title>License</title><link>https://jupitararay.github.io/license/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jupitararay.github.io/license/</guid><description>My blog posts are released under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://jupitararay.github.io/myprojects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jupitararay.github.io/myprojects/</guid><description>Identifying Languages and Language Usage in Daru, Papua New Guinea I have been a part of a larger study involving a survey on language usage in Daru, Papua New Guinea. Papua New Guinea is known for its intensely diverse language communities. The survey, that took place in a school, displayed multitude of languages spoken by the resident students, and it also provided us with insight on the frequencies at which these languages are spoken.</description></item></channel></rss>